<makerdata>
	<adultmakers>
		<maker>
			<name>Computer Driven Microscope</name>
			<website>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/657499/fromDbox/1.html</website>
			<image>https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/657499/fromDbox/scope_dhaun.jpg</image>
			<description>
				This vintage microscope is modernized with computer-controlled stage, focus and imaging sensor to collect hundreds of photographs in a grid pattern. Photographs are taken at 20 focal planes for each field of view and the best-focused frames and these are assembled into a single mosaic. In addition, the 20 photographs are stored as a z-stack set for playback by the end-user.

				The end user is a teacher or student learning microscopic identification skills as a medical professional. The learning interface  is a web-based virtual microscope allowing views of the mosaic images at various magnifications. The mosaic is mapped to the z-stacks to allow the user to explore the focal planes as you would with an actual microscope.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Darkwater FX</name>
			<website>https://www.facebook.com/Darkwater-FX-1510013975957672/</website>
			<image>https://www.facebook.com/pg/Darkwater-FX-1510013975957672/photos/?ref=page_internal</image>
			<description>
				We are a Creature make-up FX and prop design studio based in the New Orleans are. We can create everything from foam latex zombie prosthetics, to full creature suits, we also fabricate props for every occasion, haunted houses, costumes, movies, or just something cool to hang around the house.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Homemade Arcade</name>
			<website>http://www.twitter.com/olingallet</website>
			<image></image>
			<description>
				I make arcade games and ways to play them.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Krewe of Ingress</name>
			<website>http://www.google.com</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				We make swag and specialty ingress designs to support our local krewe and teammates in the field.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Krewe of Ingress: Shapers Bandoleer</name>
			<website>http://www.google.com</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				We will make Chewbacchus Bandoleers for our mighty shadow army.  Come open your mind to the enlightenment of the Shapers.

				Will also have krewe art block blanks available to be painted or decorated.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Polishedbrand</name>
			<website>https://www.pinterest.com/polishedbrand/</website>
			<image>NOTING</image>
			<description>
				Fashion design for the designer inclined.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>R2d2 replica and various hand made puppets</name>
			<website>http://www.google.com</website>
			<image>NOTING</image>
			<description>
				R2d2 replica and various hand made puppets
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Spa Cafe NOLA</name>
			<website>https://www.etsy.com/shop/SpaCafeNOLA?ref=hdr_shop_menu</website>
			<image>https://c1.staticflickr.com/9/8566/27822532224_a23891fbf7_c.jpg</image>
			<description>
				Handmade men's and women's bath products in scents inspired by café offerings.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Titan ARTillery</name>
			<website>http://www.facebook.com/titanartillery</website>
			<image>http://www.titanartillery.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/09/IMG_8061.jpg</image>
			<description>
				Titan ARTillery is a costume fabrication shop. Comprised of Michael Bogle and David S. White, we have over 10 years of combined costume experience. We make costumes out of all types of materials from foam, worbla, sintra, plastic, resin, and other materials.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Tulane Makerspace</name>
			<website>http://makerspace.tulane.edu</website>
			<image>https://www.facebook.com/homeschoolingheroes/photos/a.1533968520198680.1073741827.1533964213532444/1580296868899178/</image>
			<description>
				They're a makerspace.  They're at Tulane.  Titan ARTillery is a costume fabrication shop. Comprised of Michael Bogle and David S. White, we have over 10 years of combined costume experience. We make costumes out of all types of materials from foam, worbla, sintra, plastic, resin, and other materials.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>W5GAD Amateur Radio</name>
			<website>http://w5gad.org/</website>
			<image></image>
			<description>
				W5GAD. Amateur Radio. Impress your friends with your knowledge of Electronics And Radio propagation. Talk to people around the World without benefit of Phones or Internet. Have a good time with friendly  MIT  graduate, NASA Rocket Scientist, Engineers, Police Officers, Teachers, and other professionals as well as all walks of life. Everyone encouraged to be a HAM.  Our club since 1956. We will help you with classes as well as FCC license testing station to get your FCC Radio License. Available Local Ham Shack with Membership Available Radios and Repeaters. We help you get started with Information a lot less expensively than you think. We do have a lot of fun. For All Ages. 
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>X Over 0</name>
			<website>http://xover0.com/about.html</website>
			<image>https://scontent-lax3-1.xx.fbcdn.net/t31.0-8/11229575_1097679053633930_3089427024173236846_o.jpg</image>
			<description>
			X Over Zero is the studio of designers Katherine Voorhies and Duane McLemore. The studio was founded on the premise that contemporary computation and fabrication can be used to push the edges of the possible, even by fiercely independent practitioners working on a shoestring budget.  

			Our designs are born from Duane's wild-eyed mathematical experimentations, and are not complete until Katherine's eye for polish and refinement is applied through digital sculpting.

			We harnesses advanced computational design and professional 3d printing to craft objects that test the limits of current technology and are at the forefront of a new aesthetic that wouldn't otherwise be possible.  

			Our guiding principle is: if it can be made by traditional production methods, we don't design it for 3d printing. It is this principle that sets us apart from other designers and brands.

			The jewelry we design is not just flattering, it also starts conversations. The forms are delicate and intricate, but they also have an ordering logic that will keep you contemplating their beguiling complexities. 
			</description>
		</maker>
		
	</adultmakers>
	
	<youngmakers>
		<maker>
			<name>Electric Girls</name>
			<website>http://www.electricgirls.org</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				Design, build, and invent with Electric Girls! Build basic electronics projects to take home alongside our Electric Girls mentors.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Homeschooling Heroes</name>
			<website>http://homeschoolingheroes.com</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				Sharing success and shattering misperceptions about homeschooling! We'll be sharing super fantastic science projects from children in our group, ranging from elementary aged through high school.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>Mini Art Center</name>
			<website>http://www.miniartcenter.com/</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				Mini Art Center is a studio space for children and their families to have fun making art together. We are located in historic Algiers Point just a few short blocks from the ferry. We offer a variety of classes from ages 3 and up and have Open Studio times every weekend for just $5 a child :) 

				Today we will be creating a collaborative animation!
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>New Orleans Public Library- littleBits Chapter</name>
			<website>http://www.nolalibrary.org/event/240/maker-sundays-nopl-littlebits-global-chapter-meetup-every-3rd-sunday-of-the-month</website>
			<image>https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/466241904628088832/J8zbkgbB.jpeg</image>
			<description>
				New Orleans Public Library staff representing our littleBits Chapter group will come with our workshop set and synth kits for hands on building. 
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>NOLA CODE</name>
			<website>http://www.nolacode.org</website>
			<image></image>
			<description>
				We teach computer science and computer engineering to New Orleans children where they are. 
				Come learn to code, make your own games, program a robot, or even build your own smartphone.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>STEAM Challenges with St. Martin's Episcopal School</name>
			<website>http://www.google.com</website>
			<image>NONE</image>
			<description>
				STEAM Challenges 2017 with St. Martin's Episcopal

				We're back this year with all new STEAM activities to challenge and delight young makers of all ages! Come try out each of the STEAM challenges presented by St. Martin's Lower School teachers.  Get creative and earn completion stamps and fill out your Project Passport.
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>St. George EV# and NXT Robotics</name>
			<website>www.stgeorgesepiscopal.com</website>
			<image>http://www.stgeorgesepiscopal.com/Clue/Robotics-Team-Wins-New-Orleans-Qualifying-Tournament/23721</image>
			<description>
				7th and 8th grade robotics class students from St. George's School in New Orleans will present their award winning robots and science research from this year's First Lego League and World War II Museum Tournaments.  They will also present and manage our battle bots and robotics lego shooting gallery (see our hands-on activity below for more information). 
			</description>
		</maker>
		
		<maker>
			<name>The National WWII Museum Innovation Spotlight</name>
			<website>http://www.google.com</website>
			<image>NOTHING</image>
			<description>
				Big problems require big solutions. Learn the 4 things it takes to make a big solution,
			</description>
		</maker>
	</youngmakers>
</makerdata>